George Lardner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Subject File, 1959-2005 (Box 289-560)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (Box 480)
    - Armstrong v. Executive Office of the President, law review, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 480)
    - Department of Justice document destruction, 1992 (Box 480)
    - Loss of emails, 2000 (Box 481)
    - Miscellany, 1985, undated (Box 481)
    - Mismanagement of presidential records (Box 481)
      - Articles and clippings, 1993 (Box 481)
      - Notes, circa 1992-circa 1993 (Box 481)
      - Research material, 1992-1994, (2 folders) (Box 481)
    - Public Citizen, Inc. v. John Carlin, 1997-2001, (2 folders) (Box 481)
    - Public Citizen, Inc. v. John Carlin, 1997-2001, (2 folders) (Box 482)
    - Release of Eisenhower Oval Office recordings, 1997 (Box 482)
    - Seiko M. Green v. National Archives and Records Administration and John J. Carlin, 1997 (Box 482)
    - Vietnam War, 2001 (Box 482)
  - National Security Agency (Box 482)
    - Articles, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 482)
    - Notes, circa 1989-circa 1990 (Box 482)
    - Notes, circa 1989-circa 1990 (Box 483)
    - Pelton, Ronald W., 1986 (Box 483)
  - Nazi war criminals (declassification), 2001, (6 folders) (Box 483)
  - Nisqually and Puyallup tribes, invasions of privacy, 1973 (Box 483)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 484)
    - Broadcast news networks, 1971 (Box 484)
    - Miscellany, 1968-1987 (Box 484)
    - National Archives and Records Administration, Nixon presidential materials (Box 484)
      - Contested documents, 1992-1996 (Box 484)
      - National Security Council files, 2000-2002, (3 folders) (Box 484)
      - National Security Council materials release, 2000-2001, (3 folders) (Box 484)
      - National Security Council materials release, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 485)
      - Research material, 2000 (Box 485)
      - White House central files, 2001 (Box 485)
    - Nixon Presidential Library proposal report, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 485)
    - Republican National Committee, Dole, Robert J., 1971-1972, 1996 (Box 485)
    - White House tapes See also Container 555, same title (Box 485)
      - Abuse of governmental power segments release, 1999 (Box 485)
      - Abuse of governmental power segments release, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 486)
      - Griffin v. United States, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 486)
      - Kutler v. Carlin and Griffin, 1997 (Box 486)
      - Litigation and release, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 486)
      - Litigation and release, 1998-2000, (4 folders) (Box 487)
      - National Archives and Records Administration excise and edit, 1998 (Box 487)
      - Research material, 1993-1997 (Box 487)
      - Subject logs, 1999-2001, (3 folders) (Box 488)
      - Washington Post Freedom of Information Act request and release, 1997-2000, (4 folders) (Box 488)
  - Notes (miscellaneous) (Box 488)
    - Arkansas, circa 1995 (Box 488)
    - Cannistraro, Vincent, circa 1990s (Box 489)
    - Chronological file, 1976-1979, 1995-1998, (5 folders) (Box 489)
    - Chronological file, 1998-1999, undated, (5 folders) (Box 490)
    - Clay, Sanford, circa 1969 (Box 490)
    - Cox [?] office feature, circa 1970s (Box 490)
    - Danielsville trial, circa 1960s (Box 490)
    - Davis, Lanny J., circa 1997 (Box 490)
    - George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 491)
    - Hatch, Orrin, circa 1990s (Box 491)
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom, 1963 (Box 491)
    - Oklahoma City, Okla., and Ruby Ridge, Idaho, circa 1995 (Box 491)
    - U.S. Senate anti-terrorism hearing, 1991 (Box 491)
  - Organized crime (Box 491)
    - "25 Years After Valachi," 1988, (3 folders) (Box 491)
    - Newark, N.J., 1965-1970 (Box 491)
    - Newark, N.J., 1965-1970, (4 folders) (Box 492)
  - Pentagon Papers and the New York Times, lawsuit, 1971 (Box 492)
  - Political organizations (Box 492)
    - Black Panther Party, 1969 (Box 492)
    - FBI documents (surveillance of organizations), 1968-1975, (2 folders) (Box 492)
    - Progressive Labor Party, 1975 (Box 492)
    - Socialist Workers Party, 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 492)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 493)
  - Prisons and sentencing reform (Box 493)
    - Capital punishment, 1994-2000, (2 folders) (Box 493)
    - Presidential pardons, 2003-2004 (Box 493)
    - Prisoners, 1996-1998 (Box 493)
    - Statistics, 1989 (Box 493)
    - United States Sentencing Commission, 1987-1998, (4 folders) (Box 493)
  - Rauh, Joseph L., Jr., 1990-1992 (Box 494)
  - Reagan, Ronald, assassination attempt, 1981 (Box 494)
  - Rossotti, Charles O., Internal Revenue Service conflict of interest waiver, 2001 (Box 494)
  - Ruby Ridge, Idaho, law enforcement siege of Weaver family residence (Box 494)
    - Articles, 1995-1998, (3 folders) (Box 494)
    - Notes (Box 494)
      - Anderson, Leroy, circa 1995-1997 (Box 494)
      - Brown, Jackie and Tour [?], 1995 (Box 494)
      - Fadeley, Kenneth, testimony, 1995 (Box 494)
      - Jury foreman, Jack Weaver, 1995 (Box 494)
      - Kahoe, Michael, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 494)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1995-1997 (Box 494)
      - Senate radio and television gallery, 1995 (Box 494)
      - Telephone interviews, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 494)
      - Telephone interviews, 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box 495)
      - U.S. Senate Judiciary subcommittee hearings, 1995, (5 folders) (Box 495)
    - Research material (Box 495)
      - Congressional Research Service report on congressional investigations, undated (Box 495)
      - FBI memo regarding Waco and Ruby Ridge sieges, 2000 (Box 495)
      - Freeh, Louis J., censure recommendation, 1992-2001, (2 folders) (Box 495)
      - Freeh, Louis J., censure recommendation, 1992-2001, (5 folders) (Box 496)
      - General, 1995-2001, (3 folders) (Box 496)
      - Kevin L. Harris v. Arthur Roderick, circa 1997 (Box 496)
      - Idaho v. Kevin L. Harris, 1997 (Box 496)
      - Idaho v. FBI Special Agent, Sniper Lon T. Horiuchi, 1997-1998, (13 folders) (Box 497)
      - Idaho v. FBI Special Agent, Sniper Lon T. Horiuchi, 1997-1998 (Box 498)
      - Justice Department report, 1994, (5 folders) (Box 498)
      - Kahoe, Michael, 1997 (Box 498)
      - Miscellany, circa 1982-circa 1996 (Box 498)
      - Siege of Weaver family residence, 1992-1995 (Box 498)
      - Suspension of FBI agents, 1995-1996 (Box 498)
      - United States v. Michael A. Brown, 1997 (Box 498)
      - United States v. Randy Weaver, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 498)
      - United States Senate Judiciary subcommittee hearings, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 499)
  - Security Financial Insurance Corp., savings and loan fraud, 1963-1964, (8 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sports betting ban (Amateur Sports Integrity Act), 2001, (2 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sports betting ban (Amateur Sports Integrity Act), 2001, (7 folders) (Box 500)
  - Sports betting ban (Amateur Sports Integrity Act), 2001, (3 folders) (Box 501)
  - Spy cases (Box 501)
    - Cooke, Christopher (Box 501)
      - Article drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 501)
      - Biographies and fact sheets, 1981 (Box 501)
      - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 501)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 501)
      - Highlights of proceedings, 1981 (Box 501)
      - Legal documents, 1981, (4 folders) (Box 501)
      - Trial exhibits, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 502)
      - Trial notes, 1981, (3 folders) (Box 502)
    - Kamplies, William, 1977-1979, (3 folders) (Box 503)
    - Lee, When Ho, Los Alamos National Laboratory, Los Alamos, N.M., 2000, (8 folders) (Box 503)
    - Lee, When Ho, Los Alamos National Laboratory, Los Alamos, N.M., 2000, (2 folders) (Box 504)
    - Martin, John L., U.S. Department of Justice, 1997, (3 folders) (Box 504)
    - Morison, Samuel Loring (Box 504)
      - Articles, 1985 (Box 504)
      - Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 504)
      - General, 1984-1986, (4 folders) (Box 504)
      - Interview notes, 1985 (Box 504)
      - Jury list, 1986 (Box 504)
      - Legal documents, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 504)
      - Trail notes, 1985, (4 folders) (Box 505)
  - Star Wars (Strategic Defense Initiative) (Box 505)
    - Miscellany, 1992-1993 (Box 505)
    - Research material, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 505)
    - Research material, 1992, (6 folders) (Box 506)
    - Saucier, Aldric, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 507)
  - Supersonic transport (SST) (Box 507)
    - Article drafts, circa 1967-circa 1970, (2 folders) (Box 507)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 507)
    - Notes, 1966-1968, (2 folders) (Box 507)
    - Research material, 1961-1969, undated, (4 folders) (Box 507)
    - Research material, 1961-1969, undated, (6 folders) (Box 508)
  - Tampa Bay Lightning (hockey team), ownership (Box 508)
    - Articles, 1994-1998 (Box 508)
    - General, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 508)
    - Kokusai Green financial records, 1996-1997 (Box 508)
  - Terrorism (Box 509)
    - 9/11 terrorist attacks (Box 509)
      - Atta, Mohamed and Immigration Naturalization Service, 2001 (Box 509)
      - Attorney-client privilege, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 509)
      - Detainees, 2001, (3 folders) (Box 509)
      - Detainees, 2001, (4 folders) (Box 510)
      - General, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 510)
      - General, 2001 (Box 511)
      - PATRIOT Act, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 511)
      - Suspects, 2001, (3 folders) (Box 511)
      - Suspects, 2001, (4 folders) (Box 512)
      - U.S. Judiciary Committee hearings, 2001, (2 folders) (Box 512)
      - World Trade Center tenants, 2001 Sept. 11 (Box 512)
    - Commission on Advancement of Federal Law Enforcement, 1996 (Box 512)
    - Cuban exiles in Miami, Fla., links to terrorism, 1975 (Box 513)
    - General, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 513)
    - Greenwich Village, New York, N.Y., townhouse explosion, 1970 (Box 513)
    - Notes and memoranda, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 513)
    - Oklahoma City Federal Building bombing, Oklahoma City, Okla., 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 513)
    - Oklahoma City Federal Building bombing, Oklahoma City, Okla., 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 514)
    - Pan Am Flight 103 bombing, 1988-1993, (4 folders) (Box 514)
    - Pan Am Flight 103 bombing, 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box 515)
    - Unabomber, Kaczynski, Ted, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 515)
    - World Trade Center bombing, New York, N.Y., 1993-1997 (Box 515)
  - Tort reform and judicial selection (Box 515)
    - Alabama (Box 515)
      - Alabama Citizens for a Sound Economy, 2000 (Box 515)
      - Articles, 1996-2000 (Box 515)
      - BMW of North America v. Ira Gore, Jr., 1994-1996 (Box 515)
      - Drafts, 2000 (Box 515)
      - The Jere Beasley Consumer Report, 2000 (Box 515)
      - Judicial candidates, 2000 (Box 515)
      - Miscellany, 1996-2000 (Box 515)
      - Notes, 2000 (Box 516)
    - Citizens Against Lawsuit Abuse, 2000 (Box 516)
    - Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 516)
    - Florida, 2000 (Box 516)
    - General, 1994-2001, (3 folders) (Box 516)
    - General, 1994-2001, (8 folders) (Box 517)
    - North Carolina, 2000 (Box 517)
    - Notes, 2000 (Box 518)
    - Printed Matter, 1991-2000, (3 folders) (Box 518)
    - Texas (Box 519)
      - "Committee on Liability Insurance and Tort Law Procedure" report, 1987 (Box 519)
      - Legislative session retrospective, 1995 (Box 519)
      - "A Mandate for Change: Lawsuit Reform in Texas," 1995 (Box 519)
      - Texans for Lawsuit Reform, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 519)
      - Texans for Public Justice report, 1997-2000 (Box 519)
  - Traficant, James (Box 520)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1999, (2 folders) (Box 520)
    - General, 1985-2001, (3 folders) (Box 520)
    - Legal documents, 1996-2001, (2 folders) (Box 520)
    - Legal documents, 1996-2001, (5 folders) (Box 521)
    - Notes, circa 2001 (Box 521)
  - United States elections (Box 521)
    - 2000 Florida vote recount (Box 521)
      - Absentee ballot disputes, (2 folders) (Box 521)
      - Absentee ballot disputes, (4 folders) (Box 522)
      - Bush-Cheney Recount Fund, (2 folders) (Box 522)
      - General (Box 522)
      - Palm Beach County, (3 folders) (Box 522)
      - Notes, (2 folders) (Box 523)
      - Supreme courts, (4 folders) (Box 523)
      - Supreme courts (Box 524)
      - Volusia County, (4 folders) (Box 524)
    - Campaigns (Box 524)
      - 1968, Wallace, George C. (Box 524)
        - Article drafts and notes, (4 folders) (Box 524)
        - Campaign material (Box 524)
        - Clippings (Box 524)
        - Clippings (Box 525)
        - Contacts (Box 525)
        - Miscellany (Box 525)
        - Newsletters (Box 525)
        - Notebooks, (3 folders) (Box 525)
        - Notebooks (Box 526)
        - Opposition material, (2 folders) (Box 526)
        - Platform (Box 526)
        - Remarks (Box 526)
        - Schedules, (2 folders) (Box 526)
        - Statements of position (Box 526)
      - 1970, Congressional races (Box 526)
        - Clerical candidates (Box 526)
        - Drinan, Robert F., Massachusetts House of Representatives race, (2 folders) (Box 526)
        - McLaughlin, John, Rhode Island Senate race (Box 526)
        - McLaughlin, John, Rhode Island Senate race, (4 folders) (Box 527)
        - Notebooks (Box 527)
        - Philbin, Philip J., Massachusetts House of Representatives race (Box 527)
      - 1972 (Box 527)
        - California primary (Box 527)
        - Florida primary, (3 folders) (Box 527)
        - Indiana primary, (2 folders) (Box 528)
        - Louisiana Senate race (Box 528)
        - McGovern, George S., (3 folders) (Box 528)
        - Michigan primary notes (Box 528)
        - Miscellany (Box 528)
        - Notes (Box 528)
        - Oregon primary notes (Box 528)
        - Wallace, George C., (2 folders) (Box 528)
        - Wallace, George C., (2 folders) (Box 529)
      - 1976 (Box 529)
        - The American Party (Box 529)
        - Carter, Jimmy, (4 folders) (Box 529)
        - Church, Frank, (2 folders) (Box 529)
        - Clippings (Box 529)
        - Florida primary, (4 folders) (Box 529)
        - Florida primary, (3 folders) (Box 530)
        - Miscellany (Box 530)
        - North Carolina primary, (3 folders) (Box 530)
        - Notes, (2 folders) (Box 530)
        - Wallace, George C., (3 folders) (Box 531)
      - 1984, Hart, Gary (Box 531)
        - Addresses (Box 531)
        - Articles and tear sheets, (3 folders) (Box 531)
        - Biographical information (Box 531)
        - Clippings and research (Box 531)
        - Democratic National Convention delegate information (Box 531)
        - Interview notes (Box 531)
        - Notes (Box 531)
        - Pool reports (Box 531)
        - Platform and fact sheets (Box 531)
        - Press releases (Box 531)
        - Schedules (Box 532)
        - Staff (Box 532)
      - 1988, Bentsen, Lloyd (Box 532)
      - 1996 (Box 532)
        - Buchanan, Pat, (11 folders) (Box 532)
        - Dole, Bob (Box 532)
        - Dole, Bob, (6 folders) (Box 533)
        - Forbes, Steve, (4 folders) (Box 533)
        - General, (2 folders) (Box 534)
        - Gramm, Phil, (11 folders) (Box 534)
        - Gramm, Phil, (5 folders) (Box 535)
        - Perot, Ross, (4 folders) (Box 535)
  - United States House of Representatives, Select Committee on Assassinations See also Containers 439-468, Kennedy, John F., assassination (Box 536)
    - Articles, 1977 (Box 536)
    - Executive session, 1977 (Box 536)
    - Kennedy, John F., assassination (Box 536)
      - Hoch, Paul, 1977-1978 (Box 536)
      - Marcello, Carlos, 1979-1980 (Box 536)
      - Miscellany, 1977-1978 (Box 536)
      - Press and clippings, 1978 (Box 536)
      - Trafficante, Santo, and Sam Giancana, 1977-1979, (2 folders) (Box 536)
      - Weisberg, Harold, 1975-1979, (2 folders) (Box 536)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., assassination (Box 536)
      - Articles, 1979 (Box 536)
      - Blakely, Robert, narrations, 1978 (Box 536)
      - Blakely, Robert, narrations, 1978 (Box 537)
      - Department of Justice report, 1977 (Box 537)
      - Hearing notes, 1978 (Box 537)
      - Notes, 1979 (Box 537)
      - Press and clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 537)
    - Legislation, 1977, (3 folders) (Box 537)
    - Legislative record, 1979-1989 (Box 537)
    - Miscellany, 1978 (Box 537)
    - Notes, 1977-1979 (Box 537)
    - Notes, 1977-1979 (Box 538)
    - Press, 1977-1978 (Box 538)
  - Wackenhut, George R., private security, 1966-1967, (4 folders) (Box 538)
  - Watergate Affair (Box 538)
    - Cover-up trial (Box 538)
      - Alphabetical file (Box 538)
        - Admissibility of tapes and transcripts, 1974 (Box 538)
        - Ancillary pleadings, 1974 (Box 538)
        - Arguments over tapes, undated (Box 538)
        - Arraignment, 1974 (Box 539)
        - Articles, 1974, undated (Box 539)
        - Bill of particulars, 1974, undated (Box 539)
        - Colson, Charles W., 1973-1974 (Box 539)
        - Cox, Archibald, 1973, 1997 (Box 539)
        - Dairy industry contributions to Nixon re-election campaign, 1972-1974 (Box 539)
        - Dean, John W., 1973 (Box 539)
        - Ehrlichman, John, 1974 (Box 539)
        - Exhibits, 1974 (Box 539)
        - Gag order, 1974, undated (Box 539)
        - Haldeman, H. R., 1974 (Box 539)
        - Hearings on pretrial motions, 1974 (Box 539)
        - House Judiciary report on Nixon impeachment, 1974 (Box 539)
        - Indictment, 1970-1974, undated (Box 539)
        - Kalmbach, Herbert, 1974 (Box 539)
        - LaRue, Fred, 1973 (Box 539)
        - Magruder, Jeb Stuart, 1974, undated (Box 539)
        - Mardian, Robert Charles, 1970-1974 (Box 540)
        - Master tape list, 1971-1973 (Box 540)
        - McCord, James W., 1974 (Box 540)
        - Mitchell, John N., 1974 (Box 540)
        - Neal, James F., 1973-1974 (Box 540)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1974, (3 folders) (Box 540)
        - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 540)
          - Daily diaries, 1973 (Box 540)
          - Injunction, 1974 (Box 540)
          - Pardon, 1974, (2 folders) (Box 540)
          - Subpoena, 1974, undated (Box 541)
        - Parkinson, Kenneth, 1974, undated (Box 541)
        - Pleadings, 1973-1974, undated (Box 541)
        - Plumbers' indictment, 1974 (Box 541)
        - Pretrial motions after Nixon pardon, 1974, undated, (3 folders) (Box 541)
        - Pretrial stories, 1974 (Box 541)
        - Public lynching ad, 1974 (Box 541)
        - Published articles, 1973-1975, 1994 (Box 541)
        - Recusal ruling, 1974 (Box 542)
        - Research material, 1972-1975, undated, (4 folders) (Box 542)
        - Rulings on motion to dismiss indictment, 1974 (Box 542)
        - Special Prosecution Force, 1973-1977, (2 folders) (Box 542)
        - Strachan, Gordon C., 1973-1974, undated (Box 542)
        - Tape transcripts, 1972-1974, (4 folders) (Box 542)
        - White House tapes, 1974 (Box 543)
        - Wiretapping, 1974 (Box 543)
        - Witnesses and unindicted co-conspirators, 1974 (Box 543)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (9 folders) (Box 543)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (7 folders) (Box 544)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (8 folders) (Box 545)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (8 folders) (Box 546)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (7 folders) (Box 547)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (7 folders) (Box 548)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (6 folders) (Box 549)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (7 folders) (Box 550)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (7 folders) (Box 551)
      - Chronological file, 1974, (4 folders) (Box 552)
    - Dean, John W., 1974, 1999-2000 (Box 552)
    - Haldemen, H.R., 1970-1973, undated (Box 552)
    - Impeachment (Box 552)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1974, 1998 (Box 552)
      - Research material, 1973-1974, 1996-1998, undated, (2 folders) (Box 552)
    - Impeachment verses indictment, 1972-1974, (4 folders) (Box 553)
    - Kalmbach, Herbert, 1973 (Box 553)
    - Krogh, Egil, 1996 (Box 553)
    - Miscellany, 1971-1974, 1992-2000 (Box 553)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 554)
      - Compensation lawsuit, 1990-2000 (Box 554)
        - Notes, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box 554)
        - Research material, 1990-2000, (4 folders) (Box 554)
        - Research material, 1990-2000 (Box 555)
      - Contested documents, 1970-1972, 1996 (Box 555)
      - Radio and television address, 1973 (Box 555)
    - The Watergate Tapes: Can You Believe What You Hear?, radio broadcast, 1973 (Box 555)
    - White House tapes, Watergate Special Prosecution Force File segment, 1973 See also Containers 485-488, White House tapes (Box 555)
  - Wedtech (firm) (Box 555)
    - Article drafts, 1978 (Box 555)
    - Biaggi, Mario, 1988 (Box 555)
    - Clippings, 1978-1988 (Box 555)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 555)
    - Ethics statues, 1981-1989, (2 folders) (Box 555)
    - Freedom of Information Act requests, 1987-1989 (Box 555)
    - General, 1974-1988, (6 folders) (Box 556)
    - Independent counsel report, 1988 (Box 557)
    - Legal documents, 1981-1989, (2 folders) (Box 557)
    - Meese, Edwin, 1981-1989, (2 folders) (Box 557)
    - Meese, Edwin, 1981-1989 (Box 558)
    - Nofziger, Franklyn C. ("Lyn"), 1977-1991, (6 folders) (Box 558)
    - Nofziger, Franklyn C. ("Lyn"), 1977-1991, (2 folders) (Box 559)
    - Notes, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 559)
    - Peres, Shimon, 1985-1988 (Box 559)
    - Trial exhibits, 1983-1987 (Box 559)
    - United States v. Wallach, 1984-1988 (Box 559)
    - Wallach, E. Robert, 1979-1988 (Box 559)
    - Wallach, E. Robert, 1979-1988, (2 folders) (Box 560)
  - Whistleblower Protection Act, 1992 (Box 560)
- Part II: Miscellany, 1956-2001 (Box 560-561)
  Correspondence, photographs, drawings, newsletters, directories, financial records, and notes.
  - Awards, 1967-1993 (Box 560)
  - The Fund for Investigative Journalism, 1991-1998 (Box 560)
  - Personal (Box 560)
    - Car accident, 1978 (Box 560)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 560)
    - Lardner children, 1968-1982 (Box 560)
    - Lardner, George E., Sr., obituary, undated (Box 560)
    - Lardner, Rosemary, 1956-1996 (Box 560)
    - Last will and testament, 1991-1992 (Box 560)
  - Photograph and illustration, undated (Box 560)
  - Speeches, 1995 (Box 560)
  - Washington Post Co. (Box 560)
    - Contact lists, 1997 (Box 560)
    - Expense accounts, 1993-1997 (Box 560)
    - General correspondence, 1963-2001, (4 folders) (Box 561)
  - Writings (Box 561)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 561)
    - Westin textbook chapter, 1978 (Box 561)